hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Krakowski and I'm so thankful
that you're here today I want to talk
about
the State of the Union the state of the
world today
in the market in the industry of mentors
trainers coaches thought leaders over
the last year I've had the privilege of
working with
thousands of mentors coaches and thought
leaders and gotten direct feedback from
them of what's stopping them what's
preventing them from succeeding and
we've helped hundreds of people create
six and even seven figures in their
businesses during that time
we've grown our business to a
seven-figure business in the last 12
months it's incredible
and I find that one thing really stops
people the most here's here's that one
thing and if you can understand this
you're going to make a lot of money
you know a couple years ago there were a
lot of different hacks and tricks and
things that we could do to make it a
whole lot easier quote unquote to make a
lot of money
the problem is this is a lot of people
are now today ready to do the things
that were working back then and they're
looking for the easy path the the the
hack
the trick the shortcut and listen I'm
all about shortcuts
like in in reality I am not
in an unethical way but if you can
shorten the amount of time that it takes
you to get a result and the quality is
about 80 to 90 percent they're you know
we're not doing heart surgery in this
business I highly recommend people if
it's effective
to take shortcuts absolutely
the problem is
the way we are today where we're at
today
a lot of the shortcuts have dried up a
lot of them don't work anymore a lot of
what did work that were shortcuts years
ago don't work
however there is a proven process that
does work every time our clients apply
it they make money
the issue that I run up against though
is that a lot of people say oh man
the amount of effort I I this is a quote
by the way from multiple people they've
said the same thing the amount of effort
that I have to put in to get the output
just isn't worth it
and I tell them well
do you want to make a million dollars oh
absolutely but I just I I can't take me
that long to do oh okay understood I
gotcha
um and so
what alternatives do you have oh none
I'm just gonna go work a job hmm okay
got it and that's usually the
conversation where a lot of people are
at and they quit and they give up
because the shortcuts don't exist
anymore they don't work how they used to
a lot of the hacks and tricks that we
used to be able to do don't work
the crazy part is they're also doing a
lot of the stuff that is ineffective
that doesn't work as well and so they're
they're actually extending and
increasing the amount of time to see
results that's something that makes me
really sad when I see people doing that
is that when they're doing all the wrong
things thinking and believing that it's
all the right stuff that's going to get
them results when there's a very simple
path that works and we have a six-step
formula that works for people if you
present your coaching step number five
really is the most important part if you
can promote and present your coaching to
people
you can grow a very successful highly
lucrative business
most people are not willing to get to
that stage right there they just want to
make money they want money handed to
them and so
in reality like that's just that's not
how business Works
um but this is why most mentors most
trainers most coaches who get started
they have all these dreams all these
ideas and they never see success it's
because they're not operating out of a
framework of reality and they're not
really doing the things that are going
to work or create results and so what we
walk people through is these six steps
if you can decide on a niche
and then write sales copy create a
landing page start promoting that
landing page to get people on your email
list and you present to those people
that are on your email list your
coaching your training your courses and
you analyze the results of those
presentations
you iterate you optimize I guess after
we analyze we could put that as a step
seven you optimize
and really what is optimization
optimization is just repeating these six
steps that's all it is
if you can do that consistently
you'll make a ton of money and you'll be
able to do so working five to ten hours
a week
it's a process that works it's a proven
process that we show people how to do if
you can create offers that are
irresistible to people and you learn how
to communicate those offers in a way
that's irresistible with your sales copy
and you promote that to people and they
make a connection with you
they'll give you their money to coach
them and to Mentor them and that's how
you grow a brand and that's how you
build a business but so often people say
it's just takes too long
it's just too much
effort
to do that and so that's what I often
hear from people is that it's just too
much effort now the ones who are
actually willing to do the work
they get results
they see the results they make the kind
of money that they want to make in a
business they get an exponentially
huge amount of results in their business
so what separates
those who succeed and those who don't
well it's a willingness to be consistent
even in the face of things maybe not
working out initially
it's a willingness to experiment it's a
willingness to try things out even if
they don't work out
just to see what happens
just to come together and to see okay
how does this audience respond to this
campaign how does this audience respond
to this campaign and here's the crazy
part now we got chat GPT which gives you
a massive amount of time Savings in the
process that we used to have to do
manually before AI popped on the scene
just nine months ago
and and yet even with these tools
people say it's just too much work
here's what I know I know that the
people that that I've worked with that
do this process they make a ton of money
and so you got to really come to grips
with the fact that it's going to be work
there is effort involved you will not
have a guarantee of success initially
you will experience struggle you will
have haters you will have Rude mean
people there's a lot of skeptical people
especially when it comes to coaching and
mentoring Netflix did a special
where they basically called all coaches
and mentors scams
crazy
and I understand where they're coming
from there's a lot of scams out there
but if you're listening to this podcast
I trust that you're somebody of
Integrity somebody who cares about
people it has a message that you know
will impact people's lives
and if you can go out there and you can
present that message in a way that
captivates people that is interesting
that draws people into where they lean
in and they want to listen and it builds
trust with them
and you sell them on your coaching
programs and you sell them on your
trainings and you don't waste time you
stop being worried or concerned about
are they going to like me or or allowing
people pleasing
to get into your brain and you stop
trying to manage and maintain other
people's feelings all the time
you know I had somebody tell me this the
other way Jeremiah don't you look at the
socioeconomic climate of today's world
and just feel guilty about the fact that
you're charging money for what you do
and the answer is I told them no I don't
and they wanted to debate this as to how
just terrible it was
of what we teach and I'm just like
listen
that's part of the
the industry that I'm in is that people
will disagree with what we're doing
there are people that believe it's wrong
to sell any kind of education or
mentorship that should be free that
should be freely given to people well
the truth is there's a lot of free
education out there to people but if
people actually want to get results they
need a mentor they need somebody who can
guide them who can direct them who can
take them by the hand and show them step
by step what to do and that's what
you're called to do if you're listening
to this podcast I truly believe that you
have a message and that you can impact
people's lives but it takes doing the
hard things it takes showing up when you
don't see results it takes being willing
to humble yourself to say what don't I
know what can I adjust what can I tweak
it takes being willing to put a campaign
out there that you think is going to
work and it doesn't work out how you
want it to you know what I did that last
week I put a webinar out there it was
called um grow your mentorship business
with AI thought it was gonna get a lot
of leads in fact we had ran four other
similar campaigns they got a ton of
leads this one flopped and I realized uh
you know what that makes sense because I
wasn't specific enough I wasn't specific
enough about the area I'm going to tweak
it in the future I'll do one that's
about either webinars or growing your
email list with AI getting a little bit
more specific and then I know that
that's going to convert that's part of
the process that's part of my process is
testing seeing what messaging resonates
with people what connects with people
how you know how many people show up we
get thousands of people that register
and nobody shows up that tells me
that maybe that topic wasn't of interest
to people let's pivot in the direction
that actually does interest people
and that's exactly what we're doing and
that's exactly what has built our
business that's exactly what will
continue to grow our business
but that's a process
that's a process of continuing to show
up without a guarantee
just to see what happens just to
experiment
just to test things out
and having the
fortitude to stay consistent even when
things don't go how we want them to
even when they might not produce the
result that we want to continue
to continue to test things out to
continue to see
what don't I know to have Relentless
curiosity like a child does
discovering I see my little seven month
old Holston discovering things every
single day in his life and that's the
level of curiosity that will make you a
ton of money in your business either
that or you need to hire somebody that
has that level of curiosity in your
business
and you might say well Jeremiah I don't
have a budget to do that well great then
you got to be that one for yourself
until you have the budget to do that see
this is where a lot of people get stuck
because they're like well can't I just
hire people to do it they figure out the
price tag oh that's too expensive great
then you need to bootstrap it you can
either hire it or you can bootstrap it
those are your two options
that you have
I'm gonna direct you the best I can if
you join us for one of our five-day
intensives that we have we got one
starting this week all about creating
and launching a highly profitable group
mentorship offer that will attract
clients to you
we'll walk you through the whole process
it's free to attend
and yet even when I put resources out
there like that people say oh it's too
hard
process is just too difficult
why is that
was it too difficult to go apply for a
job and drive to work and commute 30
minutes both ways every single day to
make a pair a paycheck that barely
allows you to live
that sounds pretty hard to me
and yet we expect
a lesser level of effort when it comes
to creating a business
you know people spend ten twenty dollars
a day on gas
but they're not willing to spend ten
dollars a day on Facebook ads
when businesses start they need millions
of dollars in capital just for r d and
testing and yet in this business of
mentoring you really only need a few
hundred bucks to test things out and yet
people say oh it's too expensive oh I
don't want to lose that I would shudder
if I lost two hundred dollars from an ad
campaign really
companies all day long are spending
thousands of dollars testing things out
and yet you expect
in your business for it to be some
different special snowflake situation
I don't mean that to be harsh but that's
that's that's kind of like a cognitive
distortion it's like okay
business
operates one way
and yet people expect when they go out
there to build a mentorship business
that they're going to somehow have a
magic wand that waves and and and Magic
that doesn't exist in reality is going
to happen for them and that if it if
that magic doesn't happen for them then
everything's wrong and horrible and it's
like
oh I'm not
I'm not sure you're living on the same
Planet as everybody else at that point
for those of y'all that are actually
willing to live on this planet and
accept how things are in the rules of
physics and finances and human behavior
you can make a ton of money
for those that operate in a fantasy
mindset of I need things to happen right
away or I'm going to quit well they get
what's coming to them failure most of
the time
and they give up and they quit and it
makes more room for those that are
actually willing to stay consistent see
that's why when you stay consistent
things work out is because all a lot of
your competitors are going to quit
before they succeed and that will make
room for you see I know for a fact that
the reason why we will succeed is we
will Outlast everybody else
and when you can Outlast everybody else
you will see success very few people are
willing to do that are you one of those
that you have what it takes to succeed
you have what it takes to discipline
yourself to be successful
or are you going to go back to your
normal life and complain about how the
barbecue on the grill isn't working in
your nagging wife needs to lose 10
pounds
that's what most men do
or are you going to complain that your
kids are keeping you awake and nothing
goes your way
that's what normal people do
by the way I get on calls with people
they tell me all this stuff
literally they verbalize what I just
said I didn't make that up these are
actually things I hear from people
and it fascinates me and yet if they got
a job offer they would relocate their
whole family to go serve that job offer
but when it comes to building a brand
when it comes to building a business
they are unwilling to do what it takes
they are unwilling to be successful they
are unwilling
to do the work
are you willing to do the work
if so then I'd love to work with you and
I'd love to talk with you you can join
the waiting list for my client growth
accelerator our coaching and mentorship
program where we help people become
millionaires
where we help you become a
multi-millionaire Mentor you don't have
to keep struggling you can be successful
is it going to be easy street no
is Success
guaranteed absolutely not because you
have to be the one to do the work if
you're willing to do the work you can
see success for you
oh but that's what people don't like
they want the same risk level of just
getting
hired at a job
the risk level is if I lose my job I can
go get hired at another job because
working a job really has no risk because
you know who's taking the risk the CEO
and founder of that company
the person who put their reputation on
the line to create the company that
you're getting hired for and yet you
think that you to do the same thing
doesn't require you to put your
reputation on the line get real realize
it's going to take doing some things
that have made you uncomfortable you may
feel sick to your stomach when it comes
to doing the things that are going to
make you a millionaire but it's worth it
and I would encourage you if you need
help you may need to work through the
mental battle that's going on your
mental health you may have had
experiences in trauma and things that
have beaten into you that you should not
be doing things this way and those are
what you need to solve in order to move
forward to create the kind of business
that you want to create
I'd love to guide you and I'd love to
direct you and I'd love to help you do
that
you can succeed I know that you can
but very few do
because of everything that I've just
shared here today very few are willing
to challenge the status quo to challenge
the thoughts in their head to challenge
how everything is and they would rather
blame and take Easy Street
when success
is right in front of them
when financial success is a mentor and a
coach
standing right in front of them but
they're unwilling to do the things of
what it takes to succeed that's what I
find is a lot of people they actually
know what to do they are not willing to
do those things
and that's what's really fascinating
about this business is why if you just
have the fortitude to stick with it you
can succeed
I'd love to help you and to take you to
the next level listen listen through
this podcast this podcast is designed to
help mentors trainers and thought
leaders succeed
we have tons of episodes I have over a
thousand videos on my YouTube channel
that can help you
and in our coaching program we meet
every single week where I provide the
support guidance and accountability to
help you reach your goals
thanks for listening
share this episode with somebody who
needs a little bit of motivation
a little bit of inspiration a little
maybe a little bit of a kick in the butt
to be more disciplined we'll talk soon
have a good one
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign